# Lee Norrell

### **Certified Welder and entry level machinist**

Alexander City, AL 35010 leenorrell22@gmail.com +1 256 252 0639

An eager student ready to learn from experienced workers in the field of welding and machinery. Will complete a task without supervision in an accurate and timely manner. Often considered an utility worker because of my ability to adapt and do what it takes to get the job done.

# Work Experience

### **Tree Service**

David Easterwood Tree Service - Alexander City, AL February 2021 to Present

I was a laborer. Which includes picking up limbs, small logs, and sweeping the job site to make it look like we were never there.

#### **Dock Hand**

Russell Lands, Inc - Alexander City, AL May 2017 to September 2020

I was a dock hand which included launching and putting up boats, pumping gas into boats, and running a cash register and doing anything that was needed of me.

### Education

#### Associate's in Welding

Central Alabama Community College - Alexander City, AL August 2019 to Present

#### High school diploma

Horseshoe Bend High School - New Site, AL August 2015 to May 2019

### Skills

- MIG welding (2 years)
- TIG welding (1 year)
- Stick welding (3 years)

### Certifications and Licenses

# Oxyfuel Cutting (OFC)

July 2021 to Present

I got my oxyfuel cutting certification at cacc so I can use a torch which is a current certification.

# CAC-A

April 2021 to Present

I have my stick groove welding certificate.

# **Plasma Arc Cutting**

April 2021 to Present

I have my handheld plasma cutting certification which goes for setting it up and using it.

### Additional Information

I'm also completing my minor in machine shop at cacc. I have experience on a milling machine and lathe as well with a blueprint and machine mathematics class.